<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><itemset><item><id>4938</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=35&amp;id=4938</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/j/u/junk-removal_1_1_2_1_1.jpg</image_url><title>$35 for 250 Pounds of Junk Removal, Including Labour, Transportation and Disposal Fee from 1-888-JUNK-VAN ($152 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Moving can be exciting and provide an opportunity for a fresh slate, but the cost of disposing of all of your unwanted items can be expensive, especially if it includes an orange sofa or a dusty shag carpet from the 70s! But fear not, Dealathons has you in mind with this fantastic deal, offering up to 250 pounds of junk removal, including labour, transportation, and disposal fee from 1-888-JUNK-VAN for only $35!
&amp;nbsp;
1-888-JUNK-VAN prides itself on being the most complete removal solutions provider available, using customer focused service with a priority on taking care of their clients over their bottom line. They hire only the best drivers, all of whom receive extensive training geared towards customer satisfaction. Junk Van is committed to reducing their environmental footprint at every turn, and they dispose of all materials with a keen focus on being environmentally friendly.
&amp;nbsp;
Take a load off your back with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal and 1-888-JUNK-VAN and dispose of your unwanted items the smart way!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
 Get Rid of Old Junk
 Professional Removal Crews
 Fast &amp;amp; Flexible Service
 Friendly, Professional Staff
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Today's Deal Does Not Expire
May Purchase 1 Voucher For Personal Use &amp;amp; Unlimited As Gifts (Limit 1 Voucher Per Household)
Voucher Is Not Valid For Hot Tub Or Pianos
Freon, Tires, &amp;amp; Propane Tanks, Mattresses, Or Elevator Use Have An Extra Charge
By Appointment Only Please Call 1 888 586 5826 Or Visit Their Website
Staff Will Contact You 15-30 Minutes Prior To Arrival
24 Hour Cancellation Is Required
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid On Taxes
Voucher Includes Junk Removal Of Up To 250 Lbs, Including Labour, Transportation, &amp;amp; Disposal Fee
Areas Serviced Include 15KM Outside Calgary
Extra Charge Of $30 Apples Beyond This Area
]]></restrictions><value>152.0000</value><price>35</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>27</bought><merchant>Junk Van</merchant><merchant_url>www.888junkvan.com</merchant_url><address>Mobile Service</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>1-888-JUNK-VAN</phone></item><item><id>4933</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4933</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/t/e/teeth_whitening_5_3.jpg</image_url><title>$49 For A Dental Hygiene Exam And Periodontal Evaluation, Full Polish And 1 Unit Of Scaling Plus $39 Credit Towards Teeth Whitening At Solo, The Dental Hygiene Spa ($249 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Maintaining proper dental hygiene is of utmost importance for overall health, and today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Solo, The Dental Hygiene Spa gives you everything you need to get a good start with a Dental Hygiene Exam with cleaning for only $49!
&amp;nbsp;
At Solo, The Dental Hygiene Spa, they take a personalized approach to evidence based dental hygiene care for each of their patients. You will receive education and prevention methods to achieve oral health and ultimately overall health. It is Solo's focus to make you relaxed and valued, and at this amazing Dealathons value, what's not to love?]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
All Services Performed By A Registered Dental Hygienist
Includes A Bonus $39 Credit towards 1 hour whitening session with herbal eye treatment
or a hand paraffin wax treatment ($139 Value) + Buy 1 Bar Of Solo Soaps And Get One Free
Free Patient Parking
Flexible Hours Available
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires July 19, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call 403.264.7656 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Additional Units Can Be Paid For At Time Of Redemption For $60 Per Unit
Insurance Accepted For Additional Treatments Only If Applicable To The Patient
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Taxes Or Gratuities
Services Cannot Be Substituted
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>395.0000</value><price>49</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>18</bought><merchant>Solo, The Dental Hygiene Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.solodentalhygienespa.com</merchant_url><address>202-1711 4th St SW</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2S 1V8</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.264.7656</phone></item><item><id>4929</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4929</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/a/face_13.jpg</image_url><title>$29 for an Organic Anti-Aging Facial From Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa ($75 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In your busy life, it is important to remember to take a time out for your self, both for improved health and to keep you energized, and today's fabulous Dealathons deal brings you an Organic Anti-Aging Facial from Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa for only $29!
&amp;nbsp;
Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa is a truly serene, multi-disciplinary centre. The  setting is calm and comfortable with an approach to health that is serious and  professional. Working together, they provide you with an integrated  approach to wellness, which makes a noticeable difference! They will guide you and help you to find the  therapy, or therapies that are right for you &amp;ndash; and they are all under  one roof. With only the best therapists, they are sure to leave you feeling rejuvenated and on your path to wellness!
&amp;nbsp;
Enjoy today's amazing Dealathons deal from Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa and experience renewal in mind, body and soul!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Valid For An Anti-Aging Facial Treatment
Convenient Location
Skilled And Certified Practitioners
Turn Back The Clock On Your Skin
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires August 18, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only
Appointments Subject To Availability
24 Cancellation Policy
Tax &amp;amp; Gratuity Not Included
Not Valid For Cash Back
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>75.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>16</bought><merchant>Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.asianbridal.ca</merchant_url><address>156-55 Castle Ridge Blvd NE</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T3J 3J8</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.354.5000</phone></item><item><id>4926</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4926</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/s/p/spider_vein_2_4.jpg</image_url><title>$49 for 4 Spider Vein Removal Treatments From Laser HQ ($600 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[It's a fact that more than 50% of women suffer from or will suffer from spider veins, and as much as many might consider them to be merely an aesthetic problem, without sufficient attention, they can lead to further complications. Free yourself of spider veins with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Laser HQ, offering laser spider vein removal of up to 4 veins for only $49!
&amp;nbsp;
Spider veins are similar to varicose veins, but generally are smaller and appear blue-ish or reddish in colour, and usually appear on the legs. While things like compression stockings can be effective to reduce spider veins, it requires months before any visible results. Laser, on the other hand, is safe, effective, and has absolutely no down time. Laser HQ uses a state of the art Laser to send bright bursts of light to remove spider veins.
&amp;nbsp;
Suffer no more from spider veins, and give your body that youthful feeling with today's amazing Dealathons deal from Laser HQ!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Treatment By Certified Practitioner
Friendly Professional Staff
Safe And Effective Treatment
Uses State Of The Art Laser Machine
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires August 14, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call For Bookings
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Valid For 4 Treatments On Areas Of Up To 3 Sq Inches (8 cm)
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Taxes And Gratuities
]]></restrictions><value>600.0000</value><price>49</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>23</bought><merchant>Laser HQ Ltd.</merchant><merchant_url>www.laserhqcalgary.wix.com/laserhqcalgary</merchant_url><address>7004 Macleod Trail SE, Unit 123 (located inside Xstatik Salon &amp; Spa)</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2H 0L3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.400.2226</phone></item><item><id>4921</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4921</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/h/2/h20-colon-cleansing_5.jpg</image_url><title>$99 for 3 Cellulite Reduction Treatments &amp; 3 Body Wraps at Tania MediSpa ($375 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Cellulite until now has been a fact of life that people live with, but with today's amazing Dealathons deal you can get rid of cellulite once and for all! For $99, you get a cellulite removal package from Tania Medi Spa!
&amp;nbsp;
Tania Medi Spa has successfully found the perfect balance between efficacy and safety in all their treatments, especially with their Cellulite reduction services. Combining rigourous research into effective treatments and a personal touch, it's no wonder that so many happy clients return and recommend Tania Medi Spa!
&amp;nbsp;
Understand what all the fuss about Tania Medi Spa is about with today's fabulous Dealathons deal!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Fast, Painless Way To Lose Inches!
Includes Complete Inch Loss Package
Get Rid Of Cellulite Permanently
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 13, 2013
By Appointment Only, Please Call 403.397.1976 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or $15 Surcharge Will Be Applied
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>375.0000</value><price>99</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>Tania MediSpa</merchant><merchant_url>WWW.CALGARYPERMANENTMAKEUP.CA</merchant_url><address>342 14th St NW</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2N 1Z7</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.263.3966</phone></item><item><id>4918</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4918</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/t/e/teeth-whitening_4_1_1__1_5.jpg</image_url><title>$89 For An In-Office Hollywood Red Carpet Laser Teeth-Whitening Treatment ($250 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If your pearly whites aren't looking as white as they used to, then today's Dealathons deal is for you! For $89, you will receive Red Carpet Hollywood teeth whitening treatment at Endearing Smiles!
&amp;nbsp;
Your smile is important; it's one of the first things you notice when  you meet someone. A whiter, brighter smile is beautiful - it can help  you feel better in public gatherings and make a memorable first  impression. However, the truth is that our smiles do not improve with age. The  colour of our teeth is influenced by a number of factors: tea, coffee,  red wine and smoking are known to stain teeth, so can extended exposure  to antibiotics. Now there are methods that work for every lifestyle and  budget &amp;ndash; from inexpensive toothpastes and whitening pens-to-go to  professional teeth whitening treatments performed by dental  professionals. Endearing Smiles uses today's teeth whitening practices by spearheading a  breakthrough technology!
&amp;nbsp;
Turn back the clock on your sparkling smile with this fabulous Dealalthons deal from Endearing Smiles and dazzle your friends with teeth that demand attention!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Safe, Effective Way To Whiten Your Teeth
Experience The Benefits Of A Hollywood Smile!
Excellent Staff And Lots Of Openings For Bookings!
Relaxing, Comfortable Experience
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 2 Additional As Gifts
Expires August 12, 2014
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Taxes Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>250.0000</value><price>89</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>16</bought><merchant>Endearing Smiles</merchant><merchant_url>www.endearingsmiles.com</merchant_url><address>Suite 200, 320-23rd Ave</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2S 0J2</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.457.0250</phone></item><item><id>4915</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4915</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/b/r/brazilian_big_9.jpg</image_url><title>$19 for a Brazilian Wax From Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa ($45 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[When it comes to waxing, the last thing you feel like doing is going it alone. Luckily, today's Dealathons deal makes this ordeal into a treat with a great offer from Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa offering a Brazilian wax for only $19!
&amp;nbsp;
Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa aims to pamper you from head to toe and to bring out your inner, natural beauty, boasting some of the most experienced, talented and qualified staff in the industry! They firmly believe that a customer&amp;rsquo;s needs are the most important, and their team is committed to meeting those needs. Don&amp;rsquo;t trust just anyone with your waxing, trust the most respected spa that Calgary has to offer! With years of experience, Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa has been impressing thousands of customers with their technique, and you can find out just how great they are for yourselves!
&amp;nbsp;
Experience smooth hairless skin with this fabulous Dealathons deal and Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa and never mess with wax again!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Years Of Experience
Committed To Excellence
Friendly, Skilled And Certified Staff
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires August 10, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only
Appointments Subject To Availability
24 Cancellation Policy
Tax &amp;amp; Gratuity Not Included
Not Valid For Cash Back
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>45.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>36</bought><merchant>Asian Bridal Design Studio &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.asianbridal.ca</merchant_url><address>156-55 Castle Ridge Blvd NE</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T3J 3J8</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.354.5000</phone></item><item><id>4907</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4907</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/l/_/l_1.jpg</image_url><title>$99 for Six Laser Hair Removal Treatments on 3 Body Parts at CDPC Calgary ($1800 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Being hair-free is as easy as today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Canadian Medi Pain, offering a 6 sessions of laser hair removal for 3 body parts for only $99!
&amp;nbsp;
Get on the hairless wave with this great deal, and as everyone knows, laser hair removal is the future of hair removal! Typically, with 6-8 sessions, your unwanted hair will be gone for good, painlessly and without any downtime. And the results speak for themselves with the amount of attention and publicity that laser hair removal has received over the past years!
&amp;nbsp;
Discover a hairless new you with today's fantastic Dealathons deal from Canadian Medi Pain!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Go Hair Free Permanently And Painlessly!
Using Cutting Edge Laser Technology
Valid For Small, Medium And Large Body Parts
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires February 7, 2015
Limit 3 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
1 Body Part: Sideburns, Upper lip, Chin, Underarms, Hands, Navel, Toes
2 Body Parts: Cheeks, Full face, Neck, Shoulders, Upper arms, Lower arms, Lower back, Areola, Abdomen, Bikini,
Brazilian, Buttocks, Feet
4 Body Parts (2 Vouchers Required): Beard (men), Full arms, Upper back (excluding shoulders), Chest (men), Upper Legs, Lower Legs
Must book in advance &amp;ndash; No Walk-ins
Open to new and existing clients
Does Not Include tax or gratuity
Must Use All Treatments On Same Areas
24-Hour cancellation policy or voucher is void
Subject to availability
Cannot be shared or transferred
Voucher has no cash value
]]></restrictions><value>1800.0000</value><price>99</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>52</bought><merchant>Canadian Medi Pain</merchant><merchant_url>www.canadianmedipain.ca</merchant_url><address>1600 90 Ave SW, Suite A207</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2V 5A8</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.452.9977</phone></item><item><id>4904</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4904</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/i/diamond-dermabrasion_3.jpg</image_url><title>$39 For A Microdermabrasion And An IPL Photofacial From The Esthetic Studio ($600 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Your skin is your body&amp;rsquo;s largest organ and it has the remarkable quality of being able to regenerate itself and keep you looking youthful. The problem is that with the use of makeup and other cosmetics, your skin does not exfoliate properly and dead skin will linger far longer on your face and increase signs of aging. Fortunately, today&amp;rsquo;s Dealathons deal brings you a solution to this problem with a microdermabrasion treatment and IPL facial from The Esthetic Studio for only $39!

Microdermabrasion is a safe and effective way to achieve glowing skin with apparent results after even just one treatment! This process involves exfoliation using tiny hardened tips to gently remove dead skin from your face with varying tips used based on the sensitivity of your skin. This method, although generally more expensive than typical microdermabrasion, is safer and produces remarkable results and at this price, it is an unbeatable value!

Give your skin a little help let your youthful, vibrant skin shine with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal and The Esthetic Studio!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Way To Maintain Or Achieve Youthful Skin
Safe And Effective
Convenient Location
Includes IPL Facial!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 6, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Book Online At www.TheEstheticsStudio.com/#!appointments
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required; Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture Without Sufficient Notice
Valid For New Clients Only
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>300.0000</value><price>39</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>40</bought><merchant>The Esthetics Studio</merchant><merchant_url>www.theestheticstudio.com</merchant_url><address>1111 6th Ave SW - Tarjan Point</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2P 5M5</zip><country>CA</country><phone>contact@theestheticstudio.com</phone></item><item><id>4895</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4895</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/e/7/e7f9eeb0aac07b6397eae06440aae7b2.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For A Colon Hydrotherapy Session With Consultation From Angelica Holistic ($95 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Many people are unaware that as important as a healthy diet is to an overall sense of well-being, so too is maintaining a clean colon an integral part of staying healthy. Fortunately, today&amp;rsquo;s Dealathons deal allows you to achieve that with a colon hydrotherapy session from Angelica Holistic for only $29!

The benefits of colon hydrotherapy are many, including disease prevention, weight loss and better digestion. It may come as a surprise to many, but an overweight person can carry up to 25kg of fecal matter in their colon that may never be disposed of because of poor digestion. Changes in ecology, in quality of food, consumption of high calorie, unbalanced food and&amp;nbsp;irregularity of mealtimes bring about an accumulation of intestinal waste, which deposits on the walls and create waste solids and incrustations, along with multiplication of parasites and worms. Colon hydrotherapy, or &amp;ldquo;colonic&amp;rdquo; can serve to remedy all of these problems and alleviate many ailments due to poor digestion!

Take the first step toward living a healthy lifestyle with today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous Dealathons deal and feel free of the excess waste you have been carrying!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location On Mountain Park SE
Great Way To Clean Out Your System And The Perfect Supplement To A Weight Loss Program!
Makes For A Great Gift!
No Discomfort During Treatment!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 1 Additional As Gifts
Includes Pre-Cleanse Phone Consultation, 45 Minute Colon Hydrotherapy Session And Optional Electrolyte Drink And Probiotic Upon Appointment For $4 Paid At Time Of Redemption
Mandatory 2 Day Prep Required, To Be Discussed During Phone Consultation
Expires May 5, 2014
Valid For Women Only
Valid For New Clients Only
Valid For Calgary Residents Only
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Appointment Required, Please Call 403.829.8980 To Book
No Saturday Appointments, Business Hours Are Monday - Wednesday 10:00-5:00, Thursday 11:00-7:00, Friday 10:00- 4:00
Please Arrive 15 Minutes Early To Complete Client Health Questionnaire, Time Will Deducted From Appointment Upon Late Arrival
24 Hour Cancellation Policy In Effect, Voucher Is Forfeited Without Sufficient Notice
No Show Will Result In Forfeiture, Appointments Cannot Be Rebooked
Minimum 3 Sessions Suggested But Not Required
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>95.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>65</bought><merchant>Angelica Holistic</merchant><merchant_url>WWW.ANGELICAHOLISTIC.COM</merchant_url><address>214 Mountain Park Drive SE</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2Z 2K3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.829.8980</phone></item><item><id>4888</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4888</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/z/u/zumba-dancing_1_1_1_1_2.jpg</image_url><title>$20 For A 20 Class Pass To Vitality Fitness Plus A 1 Hour One On One Consultation ($400 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Leading an active lifestyle and staying fit can be tough when you&amp;rsquo;re chained to a desk all day and you&amp;rsquo;ve got a busy schedule to boot, but today&amp;rsquo;s Dealathons deal gives you an easy option offering 20 boot camp classes from Vitality Fitness for only $20!

The great thing about boot camp fitness classes is that they are specifically geared towards weight loss and results and it will help you achieve your fitness goals quickly. With some of the most qualified fitness instructors that Calgary has to offer, you will be sure to shed unwanted weight in the shortest time possible! This is perfect for anyone who has difficulty staying motivated without seeing results, because it will work quickly and right before your eyes!

Get in shape this and kiss those inches goodbye with today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous Dealathons deal and Vitality Fitness!
&amp;nbsp;]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Get Fit Quickly
Stay Motivated And Keep Off The Pounds!
Group Setting Helps Achieve Your Fitness Goals
Great Instructors!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Classes Expire 3 Months From Start Of First Class
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Voucher Has No Cash Value
Cannot Be Combined With Any Other Promotions
By Appointment Only (Online Bookings Only)
Subject To Availability
Valid For New Customers Only
]]></restrictions><value>400.0000</value><price>20</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>Vitality Fitness</merchant><merchant_url>www.vitalityfitnesscalgary.com</merchant_url><address>7730 Macleod Trail SE, Unit 4R</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2H 0L9</zip><country>CA</country><phone>587.777.3378</phone></item><item><id>4881</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4881</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/0/3/03a8e7dbf32d2e406ca483a75ea9cd31.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For A Shellac Spa Manicure And Spa Pedicure From Platinum Hair Group ($65 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[When cold weather hits, you need some pampering to help you forget about the snow and freezing temperatures, and with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you'll be able to do just that with a manicure and pedicure from Platinum Hair Group for only $29!
&amp;nbsp;
Platinum Hair Group has received excellent reviews for their quality of service, attention to detail, and superb ambiance! With only the finest estheticians and a customer oriented approach, they continue to wow Calgarians time and time again! Nothing says relaxation like a manicure and pedicure, and if you're looking to give someone a gift that they can appreciate, look no further than today's fantastic deal!
&amp;nbsp;
For all your spa needs, Platinum Hair Group is the place to go, and with today's fabulous Dealathons deal, you'll be saving money while you're at it!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Enjoy A Relaxing And Rejuvenating Experience
Look Great This Winter
Conveniently Located
Give Yourself A Treat Heading Into Spring
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
By Appointment Only, Please Call 403.252.1790 To Book
May Purchase 2 Per Person And Unlimited As Gifts
Voucher Expires July 31, 2014
24 Hour Cancellation Policy Is In Effect
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
]]></restrictions><value>65.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>103</bought><merchant>Platinum Hair Group</merchant><merchant_url>www.platinumhair.ca</merchant_url><address>9160 Macleod Trail SE</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2J 0P5</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.252.1790</phone></item><item><id>4876</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4876</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/t/a/tax_return_image1_5.jpg</image_url><title>$25 for a Personal Tax Return ($70 Value) OR Buy 3 Vouchers for a Business Tax Return ($150 Value) OR Buy 6 Vouchers for a Corporate Tax Return ($300 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In today's busy world,  Accubusiness is looking to attain a position as  the leading Accounting and Consulting firm for personal accounting and small to medium sized  companies across Canada. They aim to offer their  clients the best possible service in the accounting and business  consulting industry - Accubusiness is fairly priced, affordable  with a  strong professional and personal touch.                                        ﻿
Take advantage of today's Dealathons deal and get the refund you deserve!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Don't Go It Alone With Your Tax Return!
Accredited Professionals
Convenient Phone Or Email Redemption
Save Yourself Time And Money!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires January 30, 2015
May Purchase An Unlimited Amount Of Vouchers For Personal And Gift Use
Voucher's May Be Used For Returns For 2014 Or 2015
Valid For Filing By Phone (778.839.9176) Or Email (steve@accubusiness.ca)
Taxes Included
May Stack 3 Vouchers For Business Returns Or 6 Vouchers For Corporate Returns
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>300.0000</value><price>25</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>25</bought><merchant>Accubusiness</merchant><merchant_url>www.accubusiness.ca</merchant_url><address>Redeem Via Email Or By Phone</address><city>steve@accubusiness.ca</city><state></state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>778.839.9176</phone></item><item><id>4872</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4872</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/p/i/pizzaminhas_big_1.jpg</image_url><title>$12 for $25 Worth of Pizza, Wings, Drinks and More OR $20 for $40 Worth of Food and Drinks At Best Choice Pizza ($40 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Pizza is the go-to option when you want delicious food quickly and today's amazing Dealathons deal brings you saving from Best Choice Pizza! This fabulous Calgary staple has been serving up some of the most delicious pies, drinks, and more and with this fabulous Dealathons deal, you'll be getting a great value!
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Best Choice Pizza has been serving the Calgary community for years based on a healthy diet of great food, great service, great price, and along with this amazing Dealathons value, you can be sure that you're getting the best deal in town for some of the most savoury pizzas you've ever tasted! Along with their friendly, timely service, Best Choice will help you put together the perfect pie just the way you like it!
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Enjoy your fill of pizza at Best Choice Pizza with this amazing Dealathons deal and dine well and live well!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Choose From A Delicious Variety Of Pizzas
JUST IN TIME FOR YOUR SUPER BOWL PARTY!
Valid For Takeout
Comfort Food For The Family!
Perfect For When Cooking Isn't An Option!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 1 Additional As Gift
Expires July 29, 2014
Not Valid For Delivery
Limit 1 Voucher Per Order
Valid For Food And Drinks
Must Purchase One Food Item; Limit One 2 Litre Soda Per Order
Valid Only For Option Purchased
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>40.0000</value><price>12</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>17</bought><merchant>Best Choice Pizza</merchant><merchant_url>www.clickmyslice.com/restaurants/index.php?restaurantId=444</merchant_url><address>5008 Whitehorn Drive NE, Unit#3</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T1Y 1V1</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.531.2121</phone></item><item><id>4869</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4869</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/t/a/tattoo_removal_final_1_5.jpg</image_url><title>$39 for Laser Tattoo Removal for up to 9 Square Inches at Calgary Anti-Aging Spa (Value $299) </title><description><![CDATA[A tattoo can be a great way to remember something forever, but if you ever want to forget about it, you might have a hard time getting it removed! Dealathons brings you an inexpensive way to get rid of that unwanted tattoo from Calgary Anti-Aging Spa at an amazing value!
Whether you want to get your tattoo completely removed or simply lightened in order to get new ink, Calgary Anti-Aging Spa has state of the art laser technology to suit your needs. Let their friendly Certified Laser Technicians make the process as positive and effective as possible for you!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Perfect For Removing Unwanted Tattoos Effectively
Can Also Be Used To Lighten Tattoos For Touch-Ups
Friendly, Certified Technicians
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
May Purchase An Unlimited Amount Of Vouchers For Personal Use And As Gifts
Expires January 28, 2015
Additional $10 Per Extra Square Inch Required
By Appointment Only
No Cash Back Or Credit
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required
Appointments To Be Booked Online At www.CalgaryAntiAgingSpa.com
Taxes And Gratuity Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>299.0000</value><price>39</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>42</bought><merchant>Calgary Anti-Aging Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.calgaryantiagingspa.com</merchant_url><address>101-628 12th Ave SW</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2R 0H6</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.818.2924</phone></item><item><id>4861</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4861</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/c/h/chipmaster_3_7.jpg</image_url><title>$20 for Your Choice of 3 Windshield Chip Repairs, a Crack Repair, or $120 Credit Towards a Windshield Replacement at CalAlta Auto Glass ($120 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you  have ever had a crack in your windshield, then you know that there is no  predicting when it might happen. Loose rocks on the highway can cause your  windshield to shatter, especially in the winter months when the cold makes it  more brittle. Luckily, with today's Dealathons deal, you can have the peace of  mind of knowing that you have this problem covered! Get $110 towards a  Windshield Replacement or 3 stone chip repairs or one crack repair for only $20 from Cal-Alta Auto Glass! 
&amp;nbsp;
Windshield  cracks can spread very quickly, so if you have even a small crack in your  windshield, get it taken care of right away! Cal-Alta performs thousands of  safe glass replacements every year with a crew of professionally trained staff  to ensure you are well taken care of. Cal-Alta uses only OEM rated adhesives  and rust-inhibiting primers for all of their repairs and installations with the  best practices in the industry to guarantee the safety and satisfaction of all  their customers.
&amp;nbsp;
Whatever  the issue may be, don't delay on fixing that crack any longer! Get it fixed  right with today's fabulous Dealathons deal and Cal-Alta Auto Glass!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Valid At 2 Locations, Bay 8 3927 Edmonton Trail NE (T:403.291.7020) &amp; 9827 Horton Road SW (T:403.252.5050)
Voucher Can Be Used On Any Make And Model
Very Experienced &amp;amp; Knowledgeable Staff
Only The Best Equipment Used
 ]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
May Purchase An Unlimited Amount Of Vouchers For Personal And Gift Use
Limit Of 1 Voucher Per Visit
Valid For Either $120 Towards Windshield Replacement Or For Up To 3 Stone Chip Repairs Or 1 Crack Repair On Your Windshield
No Cash Back Or Credit
May Combine 2 Vouchers For Insurance Claims For A $240 Credit To Be Used Towards Your Insurance Deductible For A New Windshield Replacement
Voucher Expires January 27, 2015
Please Provide 24 Hour Cancellation Notice Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Appointment Required For Windshield Replacements Only
Tax Is Not Included
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>120.0000</value><price>20</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>56</bought><merchant>Cal-Alta Auto Glass</merchant><merchant_url>www.calaltaglass.com</merchant_url><address>Bay 8 3927 Edmonton Trail NE</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2E 6T1</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.291.7020</phone></item><item><id>4857</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4857</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/5/a/5acfe104377f389c550f23645b9f2714.jpg</image_url><title>$27 For An Express Interior And Exterior Car Detailing Including Hand Wash, Dry, Full Interior Vacuum And More At Supreme Shine ($79 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Winter weather can inspire pretty landscapes, but it can leave your car looking the worse for wear. Fortunately, today&amp;rsquo;s Dealathons deal takes care of you with an interior and exterior detailing package from Supreme Shine Professional Automotive Detailing for only $29!
&amp;nbsp;
Supreme Shine Automotive Detailing is committed to customer satisfaction offering uncompromising service at your convenience. Using only the best and most environmentally friendly products, they provide professional automotive maintenance with an eye for detail and will restore your vehicle to its showroom shine!/span&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
Give your car a facelift to begin the winter with today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous Dealathons deal and Supreme Shine Automotive Detailing!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Includes Interior And Exterior Detail
Perfect For Getting Your Car Looking In Top Form For Winter
Superior Workmanship
Convenient 16th St SE Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires July 24, 2014
Limit 5 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Limit 1 Per Visit
Additional $20 Charge For SUV's, Vans, Trucks, And Larger Vehicles
Voucher Is Valid For An Express Interior And Exterior Car Detailing Including Hand Wash, Dry, Full Interior Vacuum, Floor Mat Shampoo, Odour Eliminator, And Wipe Down Of Dash
Upgrade In-Store To A Full Interior Shampoo, Thorough Anti-Bacterial Scrub Of All Vinyl, Plastic And Leather Surfaces, Vinyl Protectant, Engine Steamed And Detailed For An Additional $129 (Regular Price $279)
Taxes &amp;amp; Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>79.0000</value><price>27</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>72</bought><merchant>Supreme Shine</merchant><merchant_url>www.supremeshine.ca</merchant_url><address>3824 16th St SE</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2G 3R7</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.262.6556</phone></item><item><id>4851</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4851</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/3/c/3c9b9f1ffe0ddaebdb9537c3fd404e2e.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For A Wash, Cut, Deep Conditioning Treatment, Blow Dry And Style + 50% Off Full Colour Or Highlights At Salon Ghazi ($100 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you&amp;rsquo;re in desperate need of a makeover for the end winter, Dealathons has a solution for you! Today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous deal offers everything you need for a new look; a wash, cut, style, blow dry, deep conditioning treatment and 50% off colour or partial highlights from Salon Ghazi for only $29!

Salon Ghazi is home to some of the best stylists in Calgary, specializing in modern cuts that highlight your features with a good understanding that personalization is the key to style. Their stylists listen to what you want and make it happen in ways that you won&amp;rsquo;t believe! Boasting an ambience that will make your visit as memorable as it is therapeutic, Salon Ghazi uses only the best and most cutting edge products to ensure that you receive only the finest care and no less than what you deserve.
&amp;nbsp;
Give yourself a look that will get you noticed for the fall with this amazing Dealathons deal and Salon Ghazi!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Skilled And Friendly Stylists
Experience Amazing Looks At A Great Value!
Convenient Location
Give Yourself A New Look For Winter!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires July 23, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call 587.350.5889 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Policy, Voucher Is Forfeited Without Sufficient Notice
An Extra Charge Applies For Hair Past Shoulder Length
Not Valid For Taxes And Gratuities
Cannot Be Combined With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>100.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>38</bought><merchant>Salon Ghazi</merchant><merchant_url>www.salon-ghazi.com</merchant_url><address>709 11th Ave SW, Unit #101 (Inside Medic Laser)</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2R 0E3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>587.352.7709</phone></item><item><id>4842</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4842</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/4/f/4fd343447f767b084e84c3d272a36ef9_1.jpg</image_url><title>$99 For 2 Palomar IPL Photofacials ($700 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[With age comes wisdom, but also sun spots, fine lines and wrinkles. Turn back the clock on your face with today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous Dealathons deal, offering two 60 minute Photo Facial Treatments for only $99 at Derma Vital!
&amp;nbsp;
Derma Vital uses cutting edge Palomar IPL technology to effectively treat a various array of common skin problems. Rejuvenate your skin with a safe and proven micronized current facial. The current stimulates and re-educates facial muscles to tighten while toning and lifting the skin.&amp;nbsp;This treatment results in increased facial tone and circulation with a reduction in the&amp;nbsp;appearance of facial lines, resulting in a noticeably younger looking appearance.&amp;nbsp;Best of all, it shows remarkable results after a single session!
&amp;nbsp;
Love the skin you&amp;rsquo;re in with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons Deal from Derma Vital and exude your inner radiance! &amp;nbsp;]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Way To Look Refreshed
Valid For Two 60 Minute Treatments
Amazing Value!
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires January 21, 2015
Limit 3 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call 403-249-4247 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>700.0000</value><price>99</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>37</bought><merchant>Derma Vital</merchant><merchant_url>www.dermavital.ca</merchant_url><address>2416 34 Ave #9</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2T 2C8</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403-249-4247</phone></item><item><id>4838</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4838</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/2/e/2e9830f17e9c153b59274735033b8e72_1.jpg</image_url><title>$19 For Either $200 Towards A Purchase Of Designer Prescription Eyeglasses Or Prescription Sunglasses OR $60 Off A One Year Supply Of Contact Lenses OR 15% Off Designer Sunglasses From Eye On 17th</title><description><![CDATA[For those of us who suffer from less than 20/20 vision, you know that maintaining your vision can be an expensive affair. Fortunately, Dealathons is here to repair the damages to your wallet with this fabulous deal, offering $200 towards prescription eyeglasses or prescription sunglasses, or discounts on contact lenses and designer sunglasses from Eye On 17th for only $19!

Eye On 17th is an exclusive, unique optical boutique located in the heart of 17th Avenue SW, offering one of the most extensive, high quality frames selections in the city. With exceptional staff, you always get exceptional service, and when it comes to service, they deliver with the most highly trained staff you&amp;rsquo;ll find anywhere who are able to find the perfect pair of glasses to suit your needs. Offering a relaxing, lounge style atmosphere, you can feel comfortable taking your time to decide exactly which frames you like best and work for you. Shopping is an experience here, and you will enjoy every second of it!

Make your eyewear shopping experience an enjoyable one with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal and find the pair that&amp;rsquo;s right for you at Eye On 17th!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Selection Of Designer Frames
Comfortable, Inviting And Modern Lounge Atmosphere
Valid For Frames And Lenses
Friendly, Knowledgeable Staff
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires January 20, 2015
Limit 5 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Limit 1 Voucher Per Order
Taxes Not Included
Valid Towards A Complete Pair Of Lenses And Frames
For Purchase Of Contact Lenses, Customer Must Have A Current Prescription Or May See Optometrist For A Fee
Not Valid For Accessories, Adjustments Or Repairs
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Oakley Or Maui Jim Products
]]></restrictions><value>200.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>23</bought><merchant>Eye On 17th</merchant><merchant_url>WWW.EYEON17TH.CA</merchant_url><address>103-1039 17th Avenue SW</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2T 0A9</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.398.6050</phone></item><item><id>4833</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4833</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/e/3/e37db45d96ba522cb3fd9ece79f19592.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For A 60 Minute Relaxation Massage From Felix Skin Care ($80 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In your busy life, it is important to remember to take a time out for your self, both for improved health and to keep you energized, and today's fabulous Dealathons deal brings you a 1 hour massage from Felix Skin Care for only $29!
&amp;nbsp;
Felix Skin Care is a truly serene, multi-disciplinary centre. The  setting is calm and comfortable with an approach to health that is serious and  professional. Working together, they provide you with an integrated  approach to wellness, which makes a noticeable difference! They will guide you and help you to find the  therapy, or therapies that are right for you &amp;ndash; and they are all under  one roof. With only the best therapists, they are sure to leave you feeling rejuvenated and on your path to wellness!
&amp;nbsp;
Enjoy today's amazing Dealathons deal from Felix Skin Care and experience renewal in mind, body and soul!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Includes A 1 Hour Massage
Convenient Location
Skilled And Certified Practitioners
Makes For A Perfect Gift!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires July 17, 2014
Limit 3 Vouchers For Personal Use, And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>80.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>56</bought><merchant>Felix Skin Care Clinic</merchant><merchant_url>www.felixskincare.vpweb.ca</merchant_url><address>Suite 703, 701 14th street NW</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2M 0L6</zip><country>CA</country><phone>587.352.8672</phone></item><item><id>4829</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4829</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/h/u/huge_1347792198.jpg</image_url><title>$15 For A Shellac Manicure At Amici Hair Studio, Esthetics And Spa ($45 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[When winter weather hits, you need some pampering to help you forget about the cold and rain, and with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you'll be able to do just that with a shellac manicure from Amici Hair for only $15!
&amp;nbsp;
Amici Hair has received excellent reviews for their quality of service, attention to detail, and superb ambiance! With only the finest estheticians and a customer oriented approach, they continue to wow Calgarians time and time again! Nothing says relaxation like a manicure, and if you're looking to give someone a gift that they can appreciate, look no further than today's fantastic deal!
&amp;nbsp;
For all your spa needs, Amici Hair is the place to go, and with today's fabulous Dealathons deal, you'll be saving money while you're at it!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Relaxing And Rejuvenating Experience
Excellent Atmosphere
Only The Best Estheticians
Conveniently Located On 4th Ave SW
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires July 16, 2014
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
24 Hour Cancellation Policy
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>45.0000</value><price>15</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>68</bought><merchant>Amici Hair Studio, Esthetics And Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.amicihair.ca</merchant_url><address>819 4th Ave SW</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T3G 0K5</zip><country>CA</country><phone>403.264.2238</phone></item><item><id>4814</id><market>Calgary</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=126&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4814</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/8/8/880b12b590dfa22eb2e1effd9f6a3bdf.jpg</image_url><title>$49 for a Full Body Microdermabrasian and Hydrating Body Masque From The Esthetic Studio ($189 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Your skin is your body&amp;rsquo;s largest organ and it has the remarkable quality of being able to regenerate itself and keep you looking youthful. The problem is that with the use of makeup and other cosmetics, your skin does not exfoliate properly and dead skin will linger far longer on your face and increase signs of aging. Fortunately, today&amp;rsquo;s Dealathons deal brings you a solution to this problem with a full body microdermabrasion treatment and hydrating body masque from The Esthetic Studio for $49!

Microdermabrasion is a safe and effective way to achieve glowing skin with apparent results after even just one treatment! This process involves exfoliation using tiny hardened tips to gently remove dead skin from your face with varying tips used based on the sensitivity of your skin. This method, although generally more expensive than typical microdermabrasion, is safer and produces remarkable results and at this price, it is an unbeatable value!

Give your skin a little help let your youthful, vibrant skin shine with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal and The Esthetic Studio!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Way To Maintain Or Achieve Youthful Skin
Safe And Effective
Convenient Location
Includes Hydrating Body Masque!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires July 13, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Book Online At www.TheEstheticsStudio.com/#!appointments
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required; Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture Without Sufficient Notice
Bonus Offer for Dealathons Clients: Add a Facial Masque or Oxygen Infusion Treatment for Only $19!
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>189.0000</value><price>49</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>39</bought><merchant>The Esthetic Studio</merchant><merchant_url>WWW.THEESTHETICSTUDIO.COM</merchant_url><address>1111 6th Ave SW - Tarjan Point</address><city>Calgary</city><state>AB</state><zip>T2P 5M5</zip><country>CA</country><phone></phone></item><item><id>4937</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=35&amp;id=4937</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/a/facial_1_12.jpg</image_url><title>One or Two Triple-Treatment Mini-Facial Packages with Thermal Masks and Eye Treatments at Vine Vera (Up to 86% Off)</title><description><![CDATA[Relaxation is a necessity when you've endured a biting cold winter, and with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Vine Vera, you can experience bliss with a full facial package for only $19 or get two packages for only $29!
]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location
Perfect Way To Rejuvenate
Safe, Effective Procedure
Look Great This Spring
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Valid for 1 or 2 Two Triple-Treatment Mini-Facials with Peel, Thermal Mask and Eye Treatment
Expires August 20, 2014
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Appointment Required, Please Call To Book
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>200.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>20</bought><merchant>Vine Vera</merchant><merchant_url>www.vinevera.com</merchant_url><address>1338-8882 170th Street</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T5T 4J2</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.443.1425</phone></item><item><id>4931</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4931</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/e/z/ezee_slim.jpg</image_url><title>$39 for 2 Fifteen Minute Ezee Slim Toning and Fat Reduction Sessions OR $75 for 4 Sessions at Ezee Slim ($240 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Losing weight often involves a tedious process of meticulously watching your diet and excercising more hours of the week than you have available, but today's fabulous Dealathons deal makes it easy with a great deal from Ezee Slim, offering 2 or 4 sessions of slimming for as little as $39!
&amp;nbsp;
The Ezee Slim toning and fat reduction system  is a state of the art, easy to use electronic muscle stimulator combined with a heat diathermy unit essential for figure control,  cellulite reduction and to gain a firm, shapely body. The computer controlled  circuits have been programmed to give the very best results  automatically for any body type in as little as 15 minutes, and with today's deal, you get two or four 15 minute sessions! Tone up your waist, thighs, abdomen, tummy, buttocks, bust, hips and more  all at the same time! The machine will exercise and strengthen lazy,  weak or aching muscles, so it can be especially beneficial for those who have difficulty with arthritis or joint pain which prevents regular conventional exercise.
&amp;nbsp;
Lose those pounds in fastest time possible with today's amazing Dealathons deal and feel great, look great and live great with Ezee Slim!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
 Tighten &amp;amp; Tone Muscles
Lift &amp;amp; Firm Bust, Bum, Inner Thighs and Arms 
Flatten Tummy 
Lose Stubborn Fat 
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 18, 2014
Package Includes 2 Or 4 Fifteen Minute Ezee Slim Toning And Fat Reduction Sessions
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
Voucher Cannot Be Shared
No Cash Back Or Credit
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required
Limit 2 Sessions Per Area, Areas Are Limited To Front Shoulders To Waist, Front Hips To Knees, Back Hips To Knees, And Back Hips To Shoulders
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>240.0000</value><price>39</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>2</bought><merchant>Ezee Slim</merchant><merchant_url>www.ezeeslim.ca</merchant_url><address>124 McLeod Ave</address><city>Spruce Grove</city><state>AB</state><zip>T7X 2Z7</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.619.8266</phone></item><item><id>4923</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4923</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/a/face_12.jpg</image_url><title>$149 For One Matrix IR Deep Wrinkle-Reduction And Texture Treatment OR Two ReFirme Fine Lines And Wrinkle Reduction Treatments At Tanseekers ($350 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[With age comes wisdom, but also fine lines, sun spots and more, but with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Tanseekers, you'll be able to turn back the clock on your face with a Texturizing Laser Treatment or 2 Refirme treatments for only $149!
&amp;nbsp;
Texturizing Laser Treatments are a new approach to deep wrinkles and improving the texture of the skin. It offers patients the positive results deep wrinkle reduction and texture treatment. 
&amp;nbsp;
Discover a brand new you with today's amazing Dealathons deal from Tanseekers!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Treat Aging And Sun Damaged Skin!
Rejuvenate Your Look, Treat Wrinkles, Rosacea, Enlarged Pores, Acne Scars And Uneven Skin Tone With Less Discomfort And Down Time Than Surgery!
Works By Texturizing Tiny Areas Of Your Skin One &quot;Pixel&quot; At A Time
Experience Dramatic Results With A Single Treatment!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 13, 2014
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Valid towards one Matrix IR Deep Wrinkle-Reduction Treatment or Two
Refirme Fine Lines &amp; Wrinkle reduction treatments with Syneron eMax elos
technology for face
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture
]]></restrictions><value>350.0000</value><price>149</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>20</bought><merchant>Tanseekers Plus Aesthetics</merchant><merchant_url>www.tanseekers.ca</merchant_url><address>124 McLeod Ave</address><city>Spruce Grove</city><state>AB</state><zip>T7X 2Z7</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.962.7878</phone></item><item><id>4917</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4917</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/m/a/mani-pedi_38.jpg</image_url><title>$20 for a Manicure with Gel Polish at Lola Beauty Bar Express ($35 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[When cold weather hits, you need some pampering to help you forget about the snow and freezing temperatures, and with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you'll be able to do just that with a manicure with gel polish from Lola Beauty Bar Express for only $20!
&amp;nbsp;
Lola Beauty Bar Express has received excellent reviews for their quality of service, attention to detail, and superb ambiance! With only the finest estheticians and a customer oriented approach, they continue to wow Edmontonians time and time again! Nothing says relaxation like a manicure, and if you're looking to give someone a gift that they can appreciate, look no further than today's fantastic deal!
&amp;nbsp;
For all your spa needs, Lola Beauty Bar Express is the place to go, and with today's fabulous Dealathons deal, you'll be saving money while you're at it!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Enjoy A Relaxing And Rejuvenating Experience
Look Great For Spring
Conveniently Located
Give Yourself A Treat
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 11, 2014
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book Or Visit 780.489.6993
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>35.0000</value><price>20</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>Lola Beauty Bar Express</merchant><merchant_url>www.facebook.com/lolabeautybarexpress</merchant_url><address>1182-8882 170th St</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T5T 4J2</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.489.6993</phone></item><item><id>4910</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4910</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/5/f/5fb71acb30c40b099b4bfbd34caa2e3c.jpg</image_url><title>$49 for Two Dermalogica Facials- Book Separately or as a Couple From Natural Balance Steamroom &amp; Spa ($110 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Your face is your most prized possession, so it's important to make sure you're giving it all the care it deserves. Luckily, with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you will be able to take care of your face with two Dermalogica facials for only $49 from Natural Balance Steamroom &amp; Spa!
&amp;nbsp;
Natural Balance Steamroom &amp; Spa has been dedicated to providing clients with professional,  quality services, in a relaxed and comfortable environment. From the  very first visit, clients are welcomed with opened arms and smiling  faces. Their goal is to guarantee quality work, professional expertise,  and up to date techniques, while maintaining a relaxed environment where  clients feel at ease. Their spa technicians are among the best in the city with years of expertise and a passion for they do, so you will be sure to see the results you desire!
&amp;nbsp;
Show off your healthy glow with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Natural Balance Steamroom &amp; Spa and keep your face shining brightly for years to come!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Valid For Two Dermalogica Facials
Convenient Location
Keep Your Skin Looking Healthy And Youthful!
Unbeatable Value!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 7, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call For Bookings
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture
Tax And Gratuity Not Included
Not Valid With Any Other Promotions Or Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>110.0000</value><price>49</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>33</bought><merchant>Natural Balance Steamroom &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.naturalbalancespa.ca</merchant_url><address>10114 123 St NW</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T5N 1N2</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.705.9439</phone></item><item><id>4905</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4905</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/a/8/a8b8645397c56173323be3711d5a13fa.jpg</image_url><title>$29 for Wash, Cut, Style &amp; Deep Conditioning Treatment + 30% off Full Colour or Partial Highlights From La Sirene Salon And Spa ($75 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you have ever found yourself late for work and skimping on your hair only to realize that you have a hot date after work and have to cancel because you don't want to look like a train wreck, never fear! Dealathons brings you a solution offering a full hair salon package from La Sirene Salon And Spa for only $29!

La Sirene Salon And Spa has been dedicated to providing clients with professional, quality services, in a relaxed and comfortable environment. From the very first visit, clients are welcomed with opened arms and smiling faces. Their goal is to guarantee quality work, professional expertise, and up to date techniques, while maintaining a relaxed environment where clients feel at ease. Their hairstylists are knowledgeable, skilled, and friendly, and they will leave your hair looking runway ready with each visit!

Join the &amp;ldquo;Hair Liberation Movement&amp;rdquo; with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal, and let La Sirene Salon And Spa take your bedhead and make turn it into a masterpiece!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
All Services Are Provided By A Trained &amp;amp; Experienced Professional.
Give Your Hair A Lift Whenever You Need It!
Full Range Of Other Beauty Services Available
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 1 Additional As Gift
Expires August 6, 2014
Taxes &amp;amp; Gratuities Not Included
By Appointment Only
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture
Extra Charge Applies For Hair Past Shoulder Length
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>75.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>lasirenesalon@hotmail.com</merchant><merchant_url>www.lasirenesalonandspa.com</merchant_url><address>8212-144 Ave</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T5E 2H4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.473.2066</phone></item><item><id>4891</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4891</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/m/a/manicure_3_4.jpg</image_url><title>$29 for a Shellac Manicure and Spa Pedicure from Nifty Nails Salon &amp; Spa ($85 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In the coldest months of the year, Dealathons presents a great way to let loose and relax with a shellac manicure and spa pedicure from Nifty Nails Salon &amp; Spa to revive you and give you something to smile about! And all this for only $29!
&amp;nbsp;
Nifty Nails is one of Edmonton's finest beauty spas. Each member of the team is licensed, professional and experienced in their field! Their goal is to offer top quality services for their clients at affordable prices that are as impressive as the treatments themselves . They will answer your questions, provide useful advice and address your needs with the utmost respect and attention. The health and well-being of their clients is their utmost priority and observe the industry standards for cleanliness in all their services and treatments. Their nail technicians specialize in unique, simple yet elegant nail design.
&amp;nbsp;
Whatever your tastes, when it comes to nails, Nifty Nails Salon &amp; Spa has you covered! So enjoy this fabulous Dealathons deal and show off your nails this winter!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Highly Trained Estheticians
Clean, Inviting Atmosphere
Attentive To All Of Your Needs
Great Way To Relax During The Winter Months!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires August 4, 2014
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Voided
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Taxes And Gratuities
]]></restrictions><value>85.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>23</bought><merchant>Nifty Nails Salon &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url></merchant_url><address>4744 99 St NW (Inside Tanglz Hair Studio)</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T6E 5H5</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.446.1158</phone></item><item><id>4882</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4882</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/g/o/gold_facial.jpg</image_url><title>$19 For A Cleopatra 24 Karat Gold Facial From OroGold Cosmetics ($120 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you are looking for a way to revitalize and renew your skin, then today’s luxurious Dealathons deal is for you! For only $19, you will receive a 24 Karat Gold Facial along from OroGold Cosmetics!   The Gold Facial was developed in Japan as a premium rejuvenating treatment that came with amazing results along with a hefty price tag. It is said that Cleopatra herself used gold for its beautifying and age defying properties, which she harnessed by sleeping with a gold mask. Dealathons brings you this revolutionary treatment which will lift and firm your skin, reduce the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles, and lighten and brighten your skin!   Indulge in the luxuries you deserve with today’s fabulous Dealathons deal and OroGold Cosmetics and harness the ancient beauty techniques that immortalized the likes of Queen Cleopatra!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Way To Revive Your Skin
Unbeatable Value
Convenient Location
Beat The Winter Dryness!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
May Purchase 2 Per Person And Unlimited As Gifts
Voucher Expires July 31, 2014
24 Hour Cancellation Policy Is In Effect
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
]]></restrictions><value>120.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>46</bought><merchant>OroGold Cosmetics</merchant><merchant_url>www.orogoldcosmetics.com</merchant_url><address>1755-8882 170 St (Inside West Edmonton Mall)</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T5T 4J2</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.489.3383</phone></item><item><id>4877</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4877</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/t/a/tax_return_image1_6.jpg</image_url><title>$25 for a Personal Tax Return ($70 Value) OR Buy 3 Vouchers for a Business Tax Return ($150 Value) OR Buy 6 Vouchers for a Corporate Tax Return ($300 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In today's busy world,  Accubusiness is looking to attain a position as  the leading Accounting and Consulting firm for personal accounting and small to medium sized  companies across Canada. They aim to offer their  clients the best possible service in the accounting and business  consulting industry - Accubusiness is fairly priced, affordable  with a  strong professional and personal touch.                                        ﻿
Take advantage of today's Dealathons deal and get the refund you deserve!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Don't Go It Alone With Your Tax Return!
Accredited Professionals
Convenient Phone Or Email Redemption
Save Yourself Time And Money!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires January 30, 2015
May Purchase An Unlimited Amount Of Vouchers For Personal And Gift Use
Voucher's May Be Used For Returns For 2014 Or 2015
Valid For Filing By Phone (778.839.9176) Or Email (steve@accubusiness.ca)
Taxes Included
May Stack 3 Vouchers For Business Returns Or 6 Vouchers For Corporate Returns
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>300.0000</value><price>25</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>26</bought><merchant>Accubusiness</merchant><merchant_url>www.accubusiness.ca</merchant_url><address>Redeem Via Email Or By Phone</address><city>steve@accubusiness.ca</city><state></state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>778.839.9176</phone></item><item><id>4870</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4870</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/c/h/chipmaster_8_3.jpg</image_url><title>$25 For Your Choice Of 2 Windshield Chip Repairs, or 1 Windshield Crack Repair, or $80 Towards A Windshield Replacement At Chipmaster Auto Paint Repair ($80 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you  have ever had a crack in your windshield, then you know that there is no  predicting when it might happen. Loose rocks on the highway can cause your  windshield to shatter, especially in the winter months when the cold makes it  more brittle. Luckily, with today's Dealathons deal, you can have the peace of  mind of knowing that you have this problem covered! Get $80 towards a  Windshield Replacement or crack or chip repair and more for only $25 from Chipmaster Auto Paint Repair!
&amp;nbsp;
Windshield  cracks can spread very quickly, so if you have even a small crack in your  windshield, get it taken care of right away! Chipmaster performs thousands of  safe glass replacements every year with a crew of professionally trained staff  to ensure you are well taken care of.
&amp;nbsp;
Whatever  the issue may be, don't delay on fixing that crack any longer! Get it fixed  right with today's fabulous Dealathons deal and Chipmaster Auto Paint Repair!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location
Can Be Used Towards Chip Repair, Crack Repair, Or Windshield Replacement
Very Experienced &amp;amp; Knowledgeable Staff
Only The Best Equipment Used
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Valid For Either 2 Windshield Chip Repairs (Up To 2 cm In Diameter), 1 Windshield Crack Repair (Up To 10 Inches), Or $80 Towards Windshield Replacement
Expires July 28, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call 780.461.2619 To Book
Limit 1 Voucher Per Vehicle
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Not Valid With Insurance Claims
Not Valid With Any Other Offers Or Promotions
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Taxes Or Gratuities
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>80.0000</value><price>25</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>25</bought><merchant>Chipmaster Auto Paint Repair</merchant><merchant_url>www.chipmastercanada.com</merchant_url><address>5820 90th St</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T6E 6A9</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.461.2619</phone></item><item><id>4846</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4846</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/b/b/bb5d8b3d3ffe07dfdeb674f03aa8592d.jpg</image_url><title>$19 For $225 Towards Designer Prescription Eyeglasses Or Designer Prescription Sunglasses From Prestige Vision Center</title><description><![CDATA[For those of us who suffer from less than 20/20 vision, you know that maintaining your vision can be an expensive affair. Fortunately, Dealathons is here to repair the damages to your wallet with this fabulous deal, offering $225 towards prescription eyeglasses or prescription sunglasses from Prestige Vision Center for only $19!

Prestige Vision Center is an exclusive, unique optical boutique, offering one of the most extensive, high quality frames selections in the city. With exceptional staff, you always get exceptional service, and when it comes to service, they deliver with the most highly trained staff you&amp;rsquo;ll find anywhere who are able to find the perfect pair of glasses to suit your needs. Offering a relaxing, lounge style atmosphere, you can feel comfortable taking your time to decide exactly which frames you like best and work for you. Shopping is an experience here, and you will enjoy every second of it!

Make your eyewear shopping experience an enjoyable one with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal and find the pair that&amp;rsquo;s right for you at Prestige Vision Center!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Selection Of Designer Frames
Comfortable, Inviting And Modern Lounge Atmosphere
Valid For Frames And Lenses
Friendly, Knowledgeable Staff
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires July 22, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Limit 1 Voucher Per Visit
Drop-Ins Welcome
Please Call 780.448.9999 For Inquiries
Valid For $225 Worth Of A Complete Order (Frame And Lenses) Of Designer Prescription Glasses Or Designer Prescription Sunglasses
Eye Exams, Contact Lenses And Repairs Are Available At An Additional Cost
Wheelchair Accessible
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Taxes
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>225.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>2</bought><merchant>Prestige Vision Center</merchant><merchant_url>www.prestigevisioncenter.com</merchant_url><address>5458 Calgary Trail</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T6H 4J8</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.448.9999</phone></item><item><id>4835</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4835</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/a/0/a002a69b1a4f881e258a9d34a93249b5.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For Three Blow Out Treatments; Includes Wash, Style, Deep Conditioning Treatment And Scalp Massage From La Sirene Salon And Spa ($105 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you have ever found yourself late for work and skimping on your hair only to realize that you have a hot date after work and have to cancel because you don't want to look like a train wreck, never fear! Dealathons brings you a solution offering three blow outs from La Sirene Salon And Spa for only $29!

La Sirene Salon And Spa has been dedicated to providing clients with professional, quality services, in a relaxed and comfortable environment. From the very first visit, clients are welcomed with opened arms and smiling faces. Their goal is to guarantee quality work, professional expertise, and up to date techniques, while maintaining a relaxed environment where clients feel at ease. Their hairstylists are knowledgeable, skilled, and friendly, and they will leave your hair looking runway ready with each visit!

Join the &amp;ldquo;Hair Liberation Movement&amp;rdquo; with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal, and let La Sirene Salon And Spa take your bedhead and make turn it into a masterpiece!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
All Services Are Provided By A Trained &amp;amp; Experienced Professional.
Give Your Hair A Lift Whenever You Need It!
Full Range Of Other Beauty Services Available
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 1 Additional As Gift
Expires July 17, 2014
Taxes &amp;amp; Gratuities Not Included
By Appointment Only
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>105.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>28</bought><merchant>La Sirene Salon And Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.lasirenesalonandspa.com</merchant_url><address>8212-144 Ave</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T5E 2H4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.473.2066</phone></item><item><id>4815</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4815</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/1/d/1dea3eb5a1d55eae487ba3db4544f32e_1.jpg</image_url><title>$99 For A Saphir Hair Straightening Treatment From La Sirene Salon And Spa</title><description><![CDATA[Curly, frizzy hair can be fun for a day, but making it manageable on a regular basis can be a daunting task! Luckily, with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you will be able to tame your curls with a Saphir Straightening Treatment from Sirene Salon And Spa for only $99!
&amp;nbsp;
Sirene Salon And Spa will help you safely transform coarse, frizzy, curly hair to smooth, straight and superbly shiny hair with results that will last for months! Using a proprietary treatment, they can treat your hair so you won't have to deal with defrizzing serums on a daily basis. With effects that last 2 - 6 months, you can be sure that this is the best way for you to save time, and with this fantastic deal, save money while you're at it!
&amp;nbsp;
Give your hair some breathing room with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Sirene Salon And Spa and keep your unruly hair tame and docile and looking silky smooth!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Smoothen Frizz And Curls For Months
Safe, Effective Treatment
Convenient Location
Friendly, Knowledgeable Staff!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 1 Additional As Gift
Expires July 13, 2014
Taxes &amp;amp; Gratuities Not Included
Limit 1 Voucher Per Visit
By Appointment Only
Extra Charge Applies For Hair Longer Than Shoulder Length
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>300.0000</value><price>99</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>36</bought><merchant>La Sirene Salon And Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.lasirenesalonandspa.com</merchant_url><address>8212-144 Ave</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T5E 2H4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.473.2066</phone></item><item><id>4811</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4811</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/a/fa4b876726d0a4c111b73d078561ee49_1.jpg</image_url><title>$39 For Two Photo Facial Treatments From Orchid Laser ($250 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[With age comes wisdom, but also sun spots, fine lines and wrinkles.Turn back the clock on your face with today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous Dealathons deal, offering two Photo Facials from Orchid Laser for only $39!
&amp;nbsp;
Orchid Laser uses cutting edge technology to effectively treat a various array of common skin problems. Rejuvenate your skin with a safe and proven treatment! This amazing new treatment will tighten and lift your skin and results in increased facial tone and circulation with a reduction in the&amp;nbsp;appearance of facial lines, resulting in a noticeably younger looking appearance.&amp;nbsp;Best of all, it shows remarkable results after a single session!
&amp;nbsp;
Love the skin you&amp;rsquo;re in with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons Deal from Orchid Laser and exude your inner radiance! &amp;nbsp;]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location
Excellent Technicians And Friendly Staff
State Of The Art Photo Facial Technology
Visible Results In Just One Treatment!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires July 10, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
Voucher Cannot Be Shared
No Cash Back Or Credit
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required
Taxes And Gratuity Not Inlcuded
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>250.0000</value><price>39</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>33</bought><merchant>Orchid Laser</merchant><merchant_url>www.orchidlaseredmonton.com</merchant_url><address>#208, 9074 - 51 Ave</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T6E 5X4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.423.0777</phone></item><item><id>4804</id><market>Edmonton</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=150&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4804</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/9/2/929f1277864f53ea852a21ec04e6df3d.jpg</image_url><title>$19 For A Shellac Manicure From Show Nails And Spa ($40 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[With winter weather in full swing, Dealathons presents a great way to let loose and relax with a shellac manicure from Show Nails And Spa to revive you and give you something to smile about! And all this for only $19!
&amp;nbsp;
Show Nails And Spa is one of Edmonton's hottest beauty spas. Each member of the Show Nails team is licensed, professional and experienced in their field for years! Their goal is to offer top quality services for their clients at affordable prices that are as impressive as the treatments themselves . They will answer your questions, provide useful advice and address your needs with the utmost respect and attention. The health and well-being of their clients is their utmost priority and observe the industry standards for cleanliness in all their services and treatments. Their nail technicians specialize in unique, simple yet elegant nail design, and will leave you looking stunning! 
&amp;nbsp;
Whatever your tastes, when it comes to nails, Show Nails And Spa has you covered! So enjoy this fabulous Dealathons deal and show off your nails this winter!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Highly Trained Estheticians
Clean, Inviting Atmosphere
Attentive To All Of Your Needs
Great Way To Relax This Winter!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires May 8, 2014
Limit of 3 vouchers for personal use and unlimited as gifts
By appointment only please call for booking
24 hour cancellation policy
No cash back or credit
Not valid with other offers or promotions
Not valid for tax or gratuity
]]></restrictions><value>40.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>24</bought><merchant>Show Nails &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url></merchant_url><address>7321 101 Ave NW</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>AB</state><zip>T6A 0H9</zip><country>CA</country><phone>780.705.0095</phone></item><item><id>4936</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=35&amp;id=4936</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/o/fotolia_6820770_xs_3.jpg</image_url><title>$79 for a Luxurious Spa Package from Lavender Day Spa ($220 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If the cold weather has you feeling stressed out, find tranquil relaxation at Lavender Day Spa with today's fabulous Dealathons deal, where you will  experience the miraculous benefits of a facial, scrub and massage for only $79! 
&amp;nbsp;
Lavender Day Spa's skin rejuvenating facial will restore moisture and  improve your skin's texture and tone and have a lasting effect on your  skin.  Providing holistic and health and wellness services, you will enjoy a much needed escape from life's hectic pace. Offering a full range of spa services, you will be pampered with  luxury. 
&amp;nbsp;
]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Relaxing Spa Package To Get You Though The Winter Blues
Convenient Location
Inviting Atmosphere With Unique Ambience
Professionally Trained Therapists
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 2 As Gifts
Expires August 20, 2014
By Appointment Only
All Services Must Be Used By Same Person
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Spa Package Includes: 45 Minute Hydrating Facial, 30 Minute Body Scrub, and 30 Minute Aromatherapy Massage
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>220.0000</value><price>79</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>20</bought><merchant>Lavender Day Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.lavenderdayspa.ca</merchant_url><address>2469 Yonge Street (2nd Floor)</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M4P 2H6</zip><country>CA</country><phone>647.347.8696</phone></item><item><id>4932</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4932</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/e/feet1_1_1.jpg</image_url><title>$199 for 3 Laser Nail Fungus Treatment on One Hand or Foot ($888 Value) or $249 for 3 Laser Nail Fungus Treatment on both Hands or Feet at North York Medical Centre ($1158 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Using FOX Diode Laser Machine; Complete Results In 3 Treatments!
State Of The Art Laser Technology Approved By Health Canada
Use This Voucher For One Or Both Feet!
Never Be Afraid To Show Off Your Hands Or Feet Again!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires August 19, 2014
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Available 5 Days A Week From Friday - Tuesday, Please Call To Book
Results May Vary, To Achieve Best Results Patients Should Consider A Fungusin Topical Medication That Is Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
24 Hour Cancellation Policy, Voucher Subject To Forfeiture Without Sufficient Notice
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>1158.0000</value><price>199</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>15</bought><merchant>NYMREC</merchant><merchant_url>www.fungusclinic.com</merchant_url><address>4646 Dufferin St, Unit #3</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M3H 5S4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.667.8808</phone></item><item><id>4930</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4930</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/a/facial_1_11.jpg</image_url><title>$89 for an Isolaz Acne Laser Treament with Pore Purification Masque From Clarity MedSpa ($245 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Acne and skin problems are very common and the various remedies can be expensive and sometime downright ineffective and uncomfortable. Fortunately, Dealathons brings you a new way to treat acne with today's  deal from Clarity MedSpa!
&amp;nbsp;
Acne is often caused by your follicles becoming  blocked due to increased cell production which increases the bacteria in  the skin and also the increase in the androgen hormone which is  responsible for oil production. Clarity MedSpa's Isolaz Acne system targets the bacteria that causes  acne spots and also helps reduce the oil production, therefore reducing  the acne. This system releases light that is emitted in a series of  short pulses..
&amp;nbsp;
Be free of acne and restore your face's natural, healthy look with this amazing Dealathons deal from Clarity MedSpa!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Pain Free
State-Of-Art Procedure
Friendly, Knowledgeable Staff
Restore Your Radiant, Healthy Skin
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And 2 Additional Gifts
Expires July 31, 2014
Additional $10 Per Extra Square Inch Required
Additional $20 For Each Additional Colour
Valid For First Time Isolaz Clients Only
By Appointment Only
No Cash Back Or Credit
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required
Taxes And Gratuity Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>245.0000</value><price>89</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>16</bought><merchant>Clarity MedSpa and Laser Centre</merchant><merchant_url>www.claritymedspa.ca</merchant_url><address>638 Church Street, Unit 2</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M4Y 2G3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.960.2222</phone></item><item><id>4925</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4925</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/m/a/massages_16.jpg</image_url><title>$35 for a 60 Minute Mobile Relaxation Massage From Balance To Life ($85 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Balance to Life focuses on life as a whole the spiritual, emotional,
mental and physical aspects. We use a wide variety of techniques from
gentle and deep to invigorating and reviving. We strive to get results. We
realize that physical problems can come from many things including
trauma, stress and much more so we work with you on all levels. In
focusing on the whole we also take care of your children and pets. Take
advantage of this amazing deal and get started with us today. ]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Choice of deep tissue, thai massage, hot stone alternative, stretch therapy, bamboo massage, relaxation (all massages can be performed over clothing)
Convenience at your door
Highly trained skilled and professional practitioners
Renew, restore, rejuvenate
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 5 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires October 13, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call 647.795.8160 Or Email balancetolife@live.ca To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Valid Within Toronto City Limits
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>85.0000</value><price>35</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>17</bought><merchant>Balance To Life</merchant><merchant_url>www.balancetolife.ca</merchant_url><address>Mobile Service</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>647.795.8160</phone></item><item><id>4922</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4922</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/m/i/mink-eyelash_1_4.jpg</image_url><title>$49 for a Full Set Of Mink Eyelash Extensions From Fraiche Salon ($160 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you've ever wondered what it is that makes those A-list celebrities look so stunning on the red carpet when their candid photos in sweatsuits are underwhelming, the answer is usually a good makeup artist, and a hefty budget. But with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you can experience the glamour without denting your wallet at Fraiche Salon, offering mink eyelash extensions for only $49!
&amp;nbsp;
Mink eyelash extensions are so sought after because of the natural look, feel, and weight that they have. With synthetic lashes, you'll quite often feel irritation and they won't last nearly as long. Mink lashes can last up to three weeks! Imagine looking stunning for weeks for this amazing Dealathons price! Fraiche Salon takes aesthetics seriously, and you can see the difference it makes when you look at the results. With so many happy Calgarians coming back to them, you'll want to get a piece of the action! And what some celebrities pay $500 for, you can get for $49!
&amp;nbsp;
Bat your eyelashes with confidence with today's fantastic Dealathons deal from Fraiche Salon and make your friends envy you with every wink!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location
Experience Hollywood Looks At A Fraction Of The Price!
No Discomfort During Application
Lasts Up To Three Weeks!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 13, 2014
By Appointment Only
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Valid For New Clients Only
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>160.0000</value><price>49</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>22</bought><merchant>Fraiche Salon</merchant><merchant_url>www.fraichesalon.com</merchant_url><address>19 Irwin Avenue</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M4Y 1L1</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.925.8600</phone></item><item><id>4920</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4920</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/b/e/beautiful_face_7_15.jpg</image_url><title>$79 For One Year Unlimited Diamond Microdermabrasion Treatments From L Squared Salon ($1200 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[It&amp;rsquo;s a strange thing to realize that most of the dust that we find in our homes is made up of dead skin cells when you consider just how much dust there is, and when you apply that realization to keeping your skin healthy, proper exfoliation is integral to both proper hygiene and maintaining a youthful glow. Today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous Dealathons deal provides you with just what you need with a year of unlimited Diamond Microdermabrasion Treatments from L Squared Salon for only $79!

Diamond Microdermabrasion is a safe and effective way to achieve glowing skin with apparent results after even just one treatment! This process involves exfoliation using tiny diamond tips to gently remove dead skin from your face with varying tips used based on the sensitivity of your skin. This method is safe and produces remarkable results and at this price, it is an unbeatable value!

Experience a fresh new you and turn back the clock on your skin with this fantastic Dealathons deal and L Squared Salon!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Safe And Effectve
Restores Your Skin To A Youthful Shine
No Down Time
State Of The Art Technology
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
First Treatment Must Be Redeemed By August 12, 2014
Limit 1 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Valid For 1 Year Of Unlimited Diamond Microdermabrasion Facials
Appointment Required, Please Call To Book
Taxes Not Included
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture
Voucher Is Valid For 1 Year From First Visit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>1200.0000</value><price>79</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>L Squared Salon</merchant><merchant_url>www.lsquaredsalon.com</merchant_url><address>714 College St</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M6G 1C3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>647.709.5383</phone></item><item><id>4916</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4916</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/g/o/golf_7_1_1_1_1_1_1_1.jpg</image_url><title>Valentine's Activity: $29 For Three 90 Minute In-Person PGA Instructed Professional Golf Lessons And Swing Analysis Software</title><description><![CDATA[Golfing with the boss can be fun but it&amp;rsquo;s a little embarrassing if your swing is as rusty as a &amp;rsquo;67 Ford Galaxy. Nurture your golf prowess with today&amp;rsquo;s brilliant Dealathons deal, offering three 90 minute golf lessons with a CPGA certified instructor for only $29!
&amp;nbsp;
Todd Miller is a certified instructor with over 18 years of experience, and he has been instructing in the fine art of golf for some time. He has perfected his method with the assistance of high speed cameras and special software to train his pupils on how to perfect their swing. Using high tech software, you will be able to analyse your swing from home between lessons so you can see how you can improve before the next lesson! And with class sizes at 8 students or less, you'll get that personal touch you need to be swinging like a pro in no time!
&amp;nbsp;
Take the first step in improving your golf game with this fabulous Dealathons deal and impress your bosses and colleagues this season with a stroke as smooth as the side of an ice cube!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Comes with state-of-the-art software to track your handicap, game statistics and practice sessions 
Over 18 years of experience as an instructor
 Includes a Casio high-speed video of your swing
 Personalized tutorial so you can improve your golf game
 ]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 3 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires February 11, 2015
By Appointment Only
48 Hour Cancellation Policy
Includes 3 Lessons With Instructor Todd Miller At Markham Golf Dome
Golf Clubs Included, Golf Balls Not Included
Classes Are In Groups Of Up To 8 People
Taxes Not Included
]]></restrictions><value>85.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>Cyber Golf Lessons</merchant><merchant_url>www.cybergolflessons.com</merchant_url><address>Markham Golf Dome, 150 Burncrest Rd</address><city>Markham</city><state>ON</state><zip>L3R 0B7</zip><country>CA</country><phone>647.801.5468</phone></item><item><id>4908</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4908</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/8/e/8e8afcb6d38d1f57e99199b491a5c3c2.jpg</image_url><title>$39 for 3 Hours of Professional House Cleaning at The Cleaning Genie (Value $150)</title><description><![CDATA[When you're home is lacking that clean feeling, it doesn't feel like home anymore. But rather than slave away to make it clean, why not take advantage of today's amazing Dealathons deal? For only $39, you will receive 3 hours of home cleaning from The Cleaning Genie!
&amp;nbsp;
When it comes to residential cleaning, The Cleaning Genie has you covered, with only the best staff and a &quot;can-do&quot; attitude! Providing an array of home services, they take what they do seriously and aim to exceed expectations at every turn. Offering a thorough cleaning with cleaning supplies included, you can be sure that you will be satisfied with the services they provide. 
&amp;nbsp;
Restore your sense of pride in your home with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from The Cleaning Genie and keep your home looking spotless!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Professional, Courteous Staff
Thorough Service
Servicing Toronto Core, Etobicoke And Mississauga
Leave Your Cleaning To Professionals
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires August 7, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Limit 2 Vouchers Per Household
Appointment Required, Please Call 647.692.9107 Or Email info@thecleaninggenie.ca To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Service Area Includes Toronto Core (East To DVP, North To 401), Etobicoke And Mississauga
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Not Valid With Any Other Offers, Promotions Or Deals
No Cash Back Or Credit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>150.0000</value><price>39</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>35</bought><merchant>The Cleaning Genie</merchant><merchant_url>www.thecleaninggenie.ca</merchant_url><address>Mobile Service</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>647.692.9107</phone></item><item><id>4906</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4906</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/l/a/laser_tattoo_final.jpg</image_url><title>$29 for TattX Laser Tattoo Removal at Clarity MedSpa and Laser Centre ($228 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[A tattoo can be a great way to remember something forever, but if you ever want to forget about it, you might have a hard time getting it removed! Dealathons brings you an inexpensive way to get rid of that unwanted tattoo from Clarity MedSpa and Laser Centre at an amazing value!
Whether you want to get your tattoo completely removed or simply lightened in order to get new ink, Clarity MedSpa and Laser Centre has state of the art laser technology to suit your needs. Let their friendly Certified Laser Technicians make the process as positive and effective as possible for you!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Perfect For Removing Unwanted Tattoos Effectively
TATTx is the Gold Standard in Tattoo Removal
More info about TattX laser: Click Here And Click Here For Video
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And As Unlimited Gifts
Expires August 10, 2014
Additional $10 Per Extra Square Inch Required
Additional $20 For Each Additional Colour
Valid For A Laser Tattoo Removal Of Up To 9 Sq Inches
Valid For New Clients Only
By Appointment Only
No Cash Back Or Credit
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required
Taxes And Gratuity Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>228.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>15</bought><merchant>Clarity MedSpa and Laser Centre</merchant><merchant_url>www.claritymedspa.ca</merchant_url><address>638 Church Street, Unit 2</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M4Y 2G3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.960.2222</phone></item><item><id>4902</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4902</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/f/e/felix_skin_laser_1.jpg</image_url><title>$49 for 4 Spider Vein Removal Treatments From Dermedica Laser ($600 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[It's a fact that more than 50% of women suffer from or will suffer from spider veins, and as much as many might consider them to be merely an aesthetic problem, without sufficient attention, they can lead to further complications. Free yourself of spider veins with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Dermedica Laser, offering laser spider vein removal of up to 4 veins for only $49!
&amp;nbsp;
Spider veins are similar to varicose veins, but generally are smaller and appear blue-ish or reddish in colour, and usually appear on the legs. While things like compression stockings can be effective to reduce spider veins, it requires months before any visible results. Laser, on the other hand, is safe, effective, and has absolutely no down time. Dermedica Laser uses a state of the art Laser to send bright bursts of light to remove spider veins.
&amp;nbsp;
Suffer no more from spider veins, and give your body that youthful feeling with today's amazing Dealathons deal from Dermedica Laser!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Treatment By Certified Practitioner
Friendly Professional Staff
Safe And Effective Treatment
Uses State Of The Art Laser Machine
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires February 6, 2015
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call For Bookings
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Valid For 4 Spider Veins Of Up To 3 Sq Inches (8 cm)
All Treatments Must Be Used By Same Customer
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Taxes And Gratuities
]]></restrictions><value>600.0000</value><price>49</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>29</bought><merchant>Dermedica Laser &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.dermedicaspa.com</merchant_url><address>361 Eglinton Ave W</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M5N 1A3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.482.1889</phone></item><item><id>4894</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4894</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/3/5/355653418ab29ef9415b10d0054337fc.jpg</image_url><title>$25 For Your Choice Of A 60 Minute Deep Tissue, Hot Stone Or Swedish Massage OR $39 For 60 Minute Massage And Facial From Ocean Breeze Spa ($90 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In your busy life, it is important to remember to take a time out for your self, both for improved health and to keep you energized, and today's fabulous Dealathons deal brings you a 1 hour massage from Ocean Breeze Spa for only $25 or receive a massage and facial for only $39!
&amp;nbsp;
Ocean Breeze Spa is a truly serene, multi-disciplinary centre. The  setting is calm and comfortable with an approach to health that is serious and  professional. Working together, they provide you with an integrated  approach to wellness, which makes a noticeable difference! They will guide you and help you to find the  therapy, or therapies that are right for you &amp;ndash; and they are all under  one roof. With only the best therapists, they are sure to leave you feeling rejuvenated and on your path to wellness!
&amp;nbsp;
Enjoy today's amazing Dealathons deal from Ocean Breeze Spa and experience renewal in mind, body and soul!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Choice Of Deep Tissue, Hot Stone, Or Swedish Massage
Convenient Location
Skilled And Certified Practitioners
Perfect Way To Rejuvenate!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal And Gift Use, Limit 1 Per Visit
Expires February 5, 2015
By Appointment Only
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required
Valid Only For New Customers Or Customers Who Have Been Inactive For Over 3 Months
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>180.0000</value><price>25</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>47</bought><merchant>Ocean Breeze Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.ocean-breeze-spa.com</merchant_url><address>7398 Yonge St, Unit 31D</address><city>Thornhill</city><state>ON</state><zip>L4J 8J2</zip><country>CA</country><phone>289.597.3570</phone></item><item><id>4890</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4890</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/b/o/body_wrap_2.jpg</image_url><title>$19 for a Brazilian Wax From Pure Aesthetics By Izabela ($38 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[When it comes to waxing, the last thing you feel like doing is going it alone. Luckily, today's Dealathons deal makes this ordeal into a treat with a great offer from Pure Aesthetics by Izabela offering a Brazilian wax for only $19!
&amp;nbsp;
Pure Aesthetics by Izabela aims to pamper you from head to toe and to bring out your inner, natural beauty, boasting some of the most experienced, talented and qualified staff in the industry! They firmly believe that a customer&amp;rsquo;s needs are the most important, and their team is committed to meeting those needs. Don&amp;rsquo;t trust just anyone with your waxing, trust the most respected spa that Toronto has to offer! With years of experience, Pure Aesthetics has been impressing thousands of customers with their technique, and you can find out just how great they are for yourselves!
&amp;nbsp;
Experience smooth hairless skin with this fabulous Dealathons deal and Pure Aesthetics by Izabela and never mess with wax again!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Years Of Experience
Committed To Excellence
Friendly, Skilled And Certified Staff
Convenient Location
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires May 4, 2014
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only
Appointments Subject To Availability
24 Cancellation Policy
Tax &amp;amp; Gratuity Not Included
Not Valid For Cash Back
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Valid For New Clients Only
]]></restrictions><value>38.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>20</bought><merchant>Pure Aesthetics by Izabela</merchant><merchant_url>www.aestheticstoronto.com</merchant_url><address>5324 Dundas Street West Unit #2 (Located inside Salon Calypso + Spa)</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M9B 1B4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.901.4405</phone></item><item><id>4887</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4887</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/2/3/23c3ee4290aae4a51063eaa875be2f38.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For A Thalgo Classic Facial With Indian Head Massage From Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa ($165 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Rejuvenating this winter is as easy as today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa, offering a Thalgo Classic Facial and an Indian Head Massage! Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa has a reputation of reviving their clients from their busy lives with their superior services and professional staff and with today's amazing deal, you can experience it for yourself at an amazing value!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Rejuvenate And Relax!
Great Way To Let Winter Stress Dissipate!
Convenient Location
Friends, Professional Staff
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires August 3, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call 416.556.0738 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required; Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture Without Sufficient Notice
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>165.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>18</bought><merchant>Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.tinapronails.com</merchant_url><address>927 Pape Ave</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M4K 3V4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.556.0738</phone></item><item><id>4879</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4879</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/5/6/560a89adee35ecb3830e6f0b2d4b7d52.jpg</image_url><title>Valentines Day: $55 Spa Day Package for 1 or $99 for 2, Includes 20 Min Infrared Sauna, Full Body Brushing, 45 Min Relaxation Massage, 45 Min Facial at Alla Wellness &amp; Beauty Lounge Plus Lunch of Bruschetta and Salad next door at Richlee Ristorante ($260</title><description><![CDATA[If the cooler winter weather has you feeling stressed out, find tranquil relaxation at Alla Wellness with today's fabulous Dealathons deal, where you will  experience the miraculous benefits of massage to balance mind and body, and a rejuvenating facial to revitalize your skin along with an infrared sauna visit and lunch for 1 or 2 people, all for as little as $55! 
&amp;nbsp;
Alla Wellness's skin rejuvenating facial will restore moisture and  improve your skin's texture and tone and have a lasting effect on your  skin.  Providing holistic and health and wellness services, you will enjoy a much needed escape from life's hectic pace. 
&amp;nbsp;
Find the balance and vitality you have been searching for with today's  amazing Dealathons deal from Alla Wellness and release blocked energy and tension!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location Near Avenue And Hwy 401
Includes Lunch At Richlee Ristorante!
Great Way To De-Stress During Winter
Friendly, Certified And Skilled Staff
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires October 31, 2014
This Facility Has No Male Technicians And As A Result, This Offer Is Valid For Women Only
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
By Appointment Only, Please Call 416.388.3330 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Not Valid With Any Other Offers Or Promotions
No Cash Back Or Credit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
Please Visit www.RichleeRistorante.com For More Information About The Restaurant
]]></restrictions><value>260.0000</value><price>55</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>56</bought><merchant>Alla Wellness And Beauty Lounge</merchant><merchant_url>www.allawellness.com</merchant_url><address>1963 Avenue Rd</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M5M 4A5</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.388.3330</phone></item><item><id>4875</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4875</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/t/a/tax_return_image1_4.jpg</image_url><title>$25 for a Personal Tax Return ($70 Value) OR Buy 3 Vouchers for a Business Tax Return ($150 Value) OR Buy 6 Vouchers for a Corporate Tax Return ($300 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In today's busy world,  Accubusiness is looking to attain a position as  the leading Accounting and Consulting firm for personal accounting and small to medium sized  companies across Canada. They aim to offer their  clients the best possible service in the accounting and business  consulting industry - Accubusiness is fairly priced, affordable  with a  strong professional and personal touch.                                        ﻿
Take advantage of today's Dealathons deal and get the refund you deserve!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Don't Go It Alone With Your Tax Return!
Accredited Professionals
Convenient Phone Or Email Redemption
Save Yourself Time And Money!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires January 30, 2015
May Purchase An Unlimited Amount Of Vouchers For Personal And Gift Use
Voucher's May Be Used For Returns For 2014 Or 2015
Valid For Filing By Phone (778.839.9176) Or Email (steve@accubusiness.ca)
Taxes Included
May Stack 3 Vouchers For Business Returns Or 6 Vouchers For Corporate Returns
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>300.0000</value><price>25</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>26</bought><merchant>Accubusiness</merchant><merchant_url>www.accubusiness.ca</merchant_url><address>Redeem Via Email Or By Phone</address><city>steve@accubusiness.ca</city><state></state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>778.839.9176</phone></item><item><id>4868</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4868</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/8/3/83e15f4101dd8fe3638fb98faa8db37e.jpg</image_url><title>$25 For A Wash, Cut, And Style Plus 50% Off Colour Services At Richmond Beauty Bar ($100 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[The winter season brings with it the opportunity to reinvent your style, and with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Richmond Beauty Bar, you can do just that with a wash, cut, and style plus 50% off colour services!
&amp;nbsp;
Richmond Beauty Bar is your one-stop go to place for all things to do with beauty. That means they know how to help you find your best look. With years of experience, an eye for what works, and the professional know-how to make it all happen, they can guarantee you'll leave the salon with a head of hair you absolutely love. And it doesn't end there; this great deal includes 50% off colour services using only the finest products on the market to top it all off!
&amp;nbsp;
Experience the difference that experience and passion makes with today's amazing Dealathons deal from Richmond Beauty Bar and you can be sure to have a great look for spring!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location
Includes 50% Off Colour Services
Experience A Hair Treatment That Will Pamper You Like No Other And Leave You Looking Stunning!
Friendly, Experienced And Professional Staff
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires July 28, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call 416.573.6193 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Policy In Effect, Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture Without Sufficient Cancellation Notice
Additional Charges Apply For Long Hair, Please Call For Details
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
Voucher Is Valid Once Deal Expires
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>100.0000</value><price>25</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>18</bought><merchant>Richmond Beauty Bar</merchant><merchant_url>www.richmondbeautybar.ca</merchant_url><address>474 Richmond St E</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M5A 1R2</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.573.6193</phone></item><item><id>4860</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4860</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/u/duct-cleaning_4_5_2.jpg</image_url><title>$59 For A Duct Cleaning Package With 20 Point Inspection, Free Sanitization, Dryer Vent Cleaning And $50 Credit Towards Furnace Cleaning From Home Air Duct Cleaning ($220 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Change of season means better weather but also dust in your home if your ducts are not properly maintained, but with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you can get a complete 20 point inspection and duct cleaning from Home Air Duct Cleaning for only$59!
&amp;nbsp;
Home Air Care Duct Cleaning provides home cleaning services in Toronto, specializing in furnaces and dryer vents. When it comes to cleaning, you want to make sure you hire the right company with the right experience and Home Air offers just that! And at this unbeatable value, you'll want to recommend this to all of your friends! Best of all, you also get $50 towards furnace cleaning!
&amp;nbsp;
Enjoy clean air in your home with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Home Air Care Duct Cleaning and breathe easy!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Valid For Up To 15 Vents
Services All Of Toronto And Surrounding GTA
Perfect For End Of Winter
Includes $50 Towards Furnace Cleaning
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires January 27, 2015
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call To Book
Valid For Up To 15 Vents And 1 Air Return
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
$9 Per Additional Vent
Service Area Includes Toronto, Mississauga, Brampton, Pickering, Ajax, Oshawa, Whitby, Markham, Richmond Hill, Vaughan, King City, Milton, Burlington, And Oakville
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid For Taxes
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>360.0000</value><price>59</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>43</bought><merchant>Home Air Care Duct Cleaning</merchant><merchant_url>www.aircaresolutions.ca</merchant_url><address>Mobile Service</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.725.1600</phone></item><item><id>4858</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4858</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/6/0/6000b971b056a099a2955703711eeb4c.jpg</image_url><title>$99 For 4 Ultra Cavitation Treatments From Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa ($500 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Cellulite until now has been a fact of life that people live with, but with today's amazing Dealathons deal you can get rid of cellulite once and for all! For $99, you get 4 ultra-cavitation treaments from Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa !
&amp;nbsp;
Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa has successfully found the perfect balance between efficacy and safety in all their treatments, especially with their ultra-cavitation services. Combining rigorous research into effective treatments and a personal touch, it's no wonder that so many happy clients return and recommend Tina Pro Nails!
&amp;nbsp;
Understand what all the fuss about Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa is about with today's fabulous Dealathons deal!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Way To Lose Inches
Safe And Effective
Convenient Location
Look Forward To A New You This Winter!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires July 24, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call 416.556.0738 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required; Voucher Is Subject To Forfeiture Without Sufficient Notice
All Treatments Must Be Used By Same Customer
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>500.0000</value><price>99</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>33</bought><merchant>Tina Pro Nails &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.tinapronails.com</merchant_url><address>927 Pape Ave</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M4K 3V4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.556.0738</phone></item><item><id>4850</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4850</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/0/c/0c59add0d1bef672e2198d5a8ef96370.jpg</image_url><title>$25 For A 1 Hour Detox Massage (Deep Tissue + Aroma Oil Massage + Hot Stone Massage) From Hue Spa ($80 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[In your busy life, it is important to remember to take a time out for your self, both for improved health and to keep you energized, and today's fabulous Dealathons deal brings you a 1 hour detox massage from Hue Spa for only $25!
&amp;nbsp;
Hue Spa is a truly serene, multi-disciplinary centre. The  setting is calm and comfortable with an approach to health that is serious and  professional. Working together, they provide you with an integrated  approach to wellness, which makes a noticeable difference! They will guide you and help you to find the  therapy, or therapies that are right for you &amp;ndash; and they are all under  one roof. With only the best therapists, they are sure to leave you feeling rejuvenated and on your path to wellness!
&amp;nbsp;
Enjoy today's amazing Dealathons deal from Hue Spa and experience renewal in mind, body and soul!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Includes Deep Tissue, Aroma Oil, And Hot Stone Massage
Convenient Yonge And Finch Location
Skilled And Certified Practioners
Hue Spa Also Provides RMT Services And Couples Massages
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 5 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires July 23, 2014
By Appointment Only
May Upgrade To An RMT Massage In Spa For Additional $19, Valid Only For New Customers
May Use 2 Vouchers For Couples Massage
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
]]></restrictions><value>80.0000</value><price>25</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>50</bought><merchant>Hue Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.huespa.ca</merchant_url><address>70 Finch Ave E.</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M2N 4R3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.229.0007</phone></item><item><id>4841</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4841</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/4/4/4427d71b487aa25a4c8439bc42163c99.jpg</image_url><title>$19 For A Diamond Microdermabrasion OR $39 For 3 Diamond Microdermabrasions From Skinful Med Spa ($240 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[With age comes wisdom, but also sun spots, fine lines and wrinkles.Turn back the clock on your face with today&amp;rsquo;s fabulous Dealathons deal, offering one or three Diamond Microdermabrasion Facials from Skinful Med Spa for as little as $19!
&amp;nbsp;
Skinful Med Spa uses cutting edge Microdermabrasion technology to effectively treat a various array of common skin problems. Rejuvenate your skin with a safe and proven facial! This treatment results in increased facial tone and circulation with a reduction in the&amp;nbsp;appearance of facial lines, resulting in a noticeably younger looking appearance.&amp;nbsp;Best of all, it shows remarkable results after a single session!
&amp;nbsp;
Love the skin you&amp;rsquo;re in with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons Deal from Skinful Med Spa and exude your inner radiance! &amp;nbsp;]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Convenient Location
Excellent Technicians And Friendly Staff
Effective Diamond Microdermabrasion Technology
Valid For One Or Three Treatments
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Expires May 21, 2014
By Appointment Only Please Call 416.593.5556 To Book
Valid For New Clients Only
No Cash Back Or Credit
24 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Taxes And Gratuity Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
]]></restrictions><value>240.0000</value><price>19</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>24</bought><merchant>Skinful Med Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.skinfulmedspa.com</merchant_url><address>250 Queen St W, 2nd Floor</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M5V 1Z9</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.593.5556</phone></item><item><id>4840</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4840</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/a/dancelife.jpg</image_url><title>$20 For 5 Classes At DanceLife Studio ($75 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Dance is a great way to express yourself, but even for beginners, it can be a great way to boost confidence and meet new people! With today's fabulous Dealathons deal, you'll have the opportunity to hone your skills no matter what skill level you are with 5 classes from DanceLife Studio for only $20!
]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Exellent Instructors
Convenient Central Location
Great For Beginner, Intermediate And Advanced Students
Meet People And Have A Great Time!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires July 20, 2014
Limit 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
To Redeem Voucher, Create A Student Profile At www.DanceLifeStudio.com And Present Voucher At First Class; Please Arrive To First Class 15 Minutes Early
Valid For New Students Only
Valid For Group Lessons Only, Please Visit Website For Current Group Class Schedule

Taxes Not Included And Payable Online Or In Person Before First Class
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>75.0000</value><price>20</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>DanceLife Studio</merchant><merchant_url>www.dancelifestudio.com</merchant_url><address>593 Yonge St, #201</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M4Y 1Z4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>855.777.7551</phone></item><item><id>4836</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4836</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/b/6/b689450a29b50a2509b25fe59f10b23e_1.jpg</image_url><title>$199 For 1 Year Of Unlimited Photofacial Treatments From Dermedica Laser And Spa ($1200 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Your skin is your body&amp;rsquo;s largest organ and it has the remarkable quality of being able to regenerate itself and keep you looking youthful. The problem is that with the use of makeup and other cosmetics, your skin does not exfoliate properly and dead skin will linger far longer on your face and increase signs of aging. Fortunately, today&amp;rsquo;s Dealathons deal brings you a solution to this problem with one year of unlimited Photofacials from Dermedica Laser &amp; Spa for only $199!

Photofacial is a safe and effective way to achieve glowing skin with apparent results after even just one treatment! This process produces remarkable results and at this price, it is an unbeatable value!

Give your skin a little help let your youthful, vibrant skin shine with today&amp;rsquo;s amazing Dealathons deal and Dermedica Laser &amp; Spa!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Way To Maintain Or Achieve Youthful Skin
Safe And Effective
Convenient Location
Valid For One Year Of Unlimited Photofacials!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
First Session Must Be Redeemed By July 17, 2014
May Purchase 1 Voucher For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
Must allow 4-6 weeks in between sessions
Must book in advance &amp;ndash; No Walk-ins
Does Not Include tax or gratuity
Expires 1 Year after activation
Subject to availability
Cannot be shared or transferred
Voucher has no cash value
]]></restrictions><value>1200.0000</value><price>199</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>25</bought><merchant>Dermedica Laser &amp; Spa</merchant><merchant_url>www.dermedicaspa.com</merchant_url><address>361 Eglinton Ave W</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M5N 1A3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.482.1889</phone></item><item><id>4820</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4820</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/a/w/aw_creations2.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For A One Hour Professional Photo Shoot At A Location Of Your Choice Including 100 High Res Printable Images On DVD, Four 5x7 Prints And Online Gallery Access From AW Creations Studio ($450 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[A picture is worth a thousand words, and with today's fabulous Dealathons deal, you'll make your memories last a lifetime! &amp;nbsp;Take time to capture your best moments with the ones you love with a professional photo shoot from AW Creations!
&amp;nbsp;
The team at AW Creations create beautiful, timeless images. Shooting with  passion, energy and creativity, each photograph tells the special  story of you! Professionalism goes a long way in photography, from everything to properly framing shots to painstaking detail in editing, AW Creations has the know-how and that passion to make your photos truly last a lifetime!
&amp;nbsp;
Take advantage of today's amazing Dealathons deal from AW Creations, and don't forget to SMILE!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Includes 4 Professionally Edited Prints!
Complete With Digital Images On DVD
Valid On Location Anywhere Within 100 Kms Of Toronto
Makes For A Perfect Gift!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
May Purchase 3 Vouchers For Personal And Unlimited For Gift Use
Expires July 14, 2014
By Appointment Only, Please Call 647.285.4391 Or Email awcreations@rogers.com To Book
Valid For A One Hour Professional Photo Shoot At A Location Of Your Choice Including 100 High Res Printable Images On DVD, Four 5x7 Prints And Online Gallery Access
Valid For Any Location Within 100 Kms Of Toronto (North To Aurora And Durham Region, Additional Charges Apply Outside These Boundaries
48 Hour Cancellation Notice Required Or Voucher Is Forfeited
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>450.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>21</bought><merchant>AW Creations Studio</merchant><merchant_url>www.awcreations.ca</merchant_url><address>Mobile Service</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip></zip><country>CA</country><phone>647.285.4391</phone></item><item><id>4791</id><market>Toronto</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=125&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4791</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/h/u/huge_1348060223.jpg</image_url><title>$20 For A 20 Class Pass To Your Choice Of Yoga-Pilates, Zumba, Bootcamp, Caribbean Rhythm Dance Fitness, Sculpt &amp; Tone, Cardio Kickboxing, SuzyMari Specialty Classes, Cardio Step Classes And More From SuzyMari Health &amp; Fitness Studio ($200 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[If you're like most people, you want to get in shape and stay in shape, but you lack the motivation and the drive to do so. Well, that's because working out can be drab and repetitious, but not with today's amazing Dealathons deal! For $20, you will be able to attend 20 dance fitness, cardio kickboxing classes and more from SuzyMari Health And Fitness Studio!
&amp;nbsp;
Are you ready to party yourself into shape? That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what Zumba is all about! It&amp;rsquo;s an exhilarating, effective, easy-to-follow,  Latin-inspired, calorie-burning dance party that&amp;rsquo;s moving  millions of people towards a healthier lifestyle! Imagine a workout that doesn't feel like a chore! Zumba combines great music that will get you moving with effective movements that are easy to follow that are designed to give you the most efficient workout for your whole body. Damidance's instructors are passionate about Zumba and fitness, and it's their passion that motivates their students towards excellence and fitness! And with this great deal, you can choose from cardio kickboxing, SuzyMari specialty classes, step classes and more!
&amp;nbsp;
Discover the joys of dance fitness and join the fun fitness revolution! Enjoy this great Dealathons deal from SuzyMari Health And Fitness Studio!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Stay Fit While Having Fun!
Experienced Teachers With A Passion For Fitness Produce The Best Results!
Makes For A Great Gift
Unbeatable Value!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
First Class Must Be Redeemed By April 2, 2014
Please Call To Book Classes
Taxes Not Included
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Valid For New Clients Only Or Clients That Have Been Inactive For 3 Months
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
]]></restrictions><value>200.0000</value><price>20</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>34</bought><merchant>SuzyMari Health &amp; Fitness Studio</merchant><merchant_url>WWW.SUZYMARI.CA</merchant_url><address>100 Westmore Dr, Unit #27</address><city>Toronto</city><state>ON</state><zip>M9V 5C3</zip><country>CA</country><phone>416.746.2431</phone></item><item><id>4935</id><market>Vancouver</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=127&amp;cid=35&amp;id=4935</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/c/e/cellulite_3_2_1_17.jpg</image_url><title>$79 for Three UltraLipo Cellulite Treatments from LeSante Spa ($384 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Cellulite until now has been a fact of life that people live with, but with today's amazing Dealathons deal you can get rid of cellulite once and for all! For $79, you get three UltraLipo cellulite removal treatments from LeSante Spa!
&amp;nbsp;
LeSante Spa has successfully found the perfect balance between efficacy and safety in all their treatments, especially with their Cellulite reduction services. Combining rigorous research into effective treatments and a personal touch, it's no wonder that so many happy clients return and recommend LeSante Spa!
&amp;nbsp;
Understand what all the fuss about LeSante Spa is about with today's fabulous Dealathons deal!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Great Way To Lose Inches
Safe And Effective
Convenient Location
Look Forward To A New You This Sping!
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires February 20, 2014
Limit 2 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Call 604.433.8480 To Book
24 Hour Cancellation Policy; Voucher Subject To Forfeiture Without Sufficient Notice
Package includes 3 thirty minute LipoLaser sessions on a body part of your choice, including tummy, love handles, arms, thighs and buttocks.
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
]]></restrictions><value>384.0000</value><price>79</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-22T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>20</bought><merchant>LeSante Spa</merchant><merchant_url>WWW.LESANTESPA.COM</merchant_url><address>#101-6411 Nelson Ave</address><city>Burnaby</city><state>BC</state><zip>V5H 3J4</zip><country>CA</country><phone>604.433.8480</phone></item><item><id>4934</id><market>Vancouver</market><url>http://www.dealathons.com/?city=127&amp;cid=37&amp;id=4934</url><image_url>http://media.dealathons.com/catalog/product/cache/4/image/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/m/i/micro-dermabrasion_2_1_2_2.jpg</image_url><title>$29 For 2 Diamond Microdermabrasion Treatments From Marquis Salon &amp; Day Spa ($180 Value)</title><description><![CDATA[Your face is your most prized possession, so it's important to make sure you're giving it all the care it deserves. Luckily, with today's amazing Dealathons deal, you will be able to take care of your face with 2 diamond microdermabrasion treatments for only $29 from Marquis Salon &amp; Day Spa!
&amp;nbsp;
Marquis Salon &amp; Day Spa has been dedicated to providing clients with professional,  quality services, in a relaxed and comfortable environment. From the  very first visit, clients are welcomed with opened arms and smiling  faces. Their goal is to guarantee quality work, professional expertise,  and up to date techniques, while maintaining a relaxed environment where  clients feel at ease. Their spa technicians are among the best in the city with years of expertise and a passion for they do, so you will be sure to see the results you desire!
&amp;nbsp;
Show off your healthy glow with today's fabulous Dealathons deal from Marquis Salon &amp; Day Spa and keep your face shining brightly for years to come!]]></description><highlights><![CDATA[
Conveniently Located In North Vancouver
Keep Your Skin Looking Healthy And Youthful!
Unbeatable Value!
Using State-Of-The-Art Diamond Microdermabrasion Techniques
]]></highlights><restrictions><![CDATA[
Expires August 19, 2014
Limit 3 Vouchers For Personal Use And Unlimited As Gifts
By Appointment Only, Please Call 604.986.5552 To Book
Not Valid With Any Other Offers
Valid For New Clients Only
Voucher Has No Cash Value
No Cash Back Or Credit
Taxes And Gratuities Not Included
48 Hour Cancellation Policy, Voucher Is Forfeited Without Sufficient Notice
]]></restrictions><value>180.0000</value><price>29</price><required_qty>0</required_qty><ending_time>2014-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</ending_time><bought>15</bought><merchant>Marquis Salon &amp; Day Spa</merchant><merchant_url>WWW.MARQUISSALON.COM</merchant_url><address>125 East 15th St</address><city>North Vancouver</city><state>BC</state><zip>V7L 2P7</zip><country>CA</country><phone>604.986.5552</phone></item></itemset>